driveragentplus.com 2019-07-15

# DriverAgent Plus Privacy Policy | Terms of Use & Tracking Cookies Explained - DriverAgentPlus.com

**Effective Date:** 2015.12.24

DriverAgentPlus.com, Inc. has been awarded Trust Guard's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by Trust Guard for compliance with Trust Guard's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. Trust Guard's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us [here](http://driveragentplus.com/support.php).

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience**  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * **To improve our website**  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * **To improve customer service**  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * **To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Customer Testimonials, Comments & Reviews

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at http://DriverAgentPlus.com/feedback.php.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at our EULA

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, or if you would like to correct, update, change, or delete your information you may contact us using the information below:

120 Water St., North Andover, MA 01845, USA
